const questions = [
    {
  number:1,        
  question:'What is Fusion ?', 
  answer:'A Drone Brand', 
  options:[
          'A Computer Brand', 
          'A Drone Brand', 
          'A Car Brand', 
          'A Mobile Brand'
          ]
    }, 
    {
            number:2,
            question: 'When was Fusion Founded ?',
            answer: '2022',
            options: [
          '2021',
          '2019',
          '2020',
          '2022'
          ]
    }, 
    {
            number:3,
            question: 'How many models do Fusion have ?',
            answer: 'Four',
            options: [
          'Five',
          'Four',
          'Ten',
          'Seven'
          ]
    }, 
    {
            number:4,
            question: 'How many colors per fusion model ?',
            answer: 'Four',
            options: [
          'Three',
          'Six',
          'Four',
          'Five'
          ]
    }, 
    {
            number:5,
            question:'What is NOT a Fusion model ?',
            answer:'Fusion S',
            options:[
          'Fusion Sky',
          'Fusion I',
          'Fusion S',
          'Fusion II'
          ]
    },
    {
            number:6,
            question:'Fusion II Price ?',
            answer:'$499',
            options:[
          '$399',
          '$499',
          '$599',
          '$699'
          ]
    },
    {
          number:7,
          question:'Fusion Sky Transmission Distance ?',
          answer:'12km',
          options:[
        '2km',
        '21km',
        '12km',
        '10km'
        ]
    },
    {
        number:8,
        question:'Fusion Ultra Flight Time ?',
        answer:'34-min',
        options:[
      '34-min',
      '54-min',
      '19-min',
      '43-min'
      ]
    },
    {
        number:9,
        question:'Not a Fusion II Color ?',
        answer:'Yellow',
        options:[
      'Red',
      'Black',
      'Yellow',
      'Blue'
      ]
    },
    {
      number:10,
      question:'Cheapest Fusion Drone ?',
      answer:'Fusion I',
      options:[
    'Fusion Ultra',
    'Fusion I',
    'Fusion II',
    'Fusion Sky'
    ]
  },

 ]
 